

OLLI-PEKKA NIKKA

Software Engineer / XR Developer

+358404115202

www.ollipekkanikka.com

ollipekkanikka@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Bootcamp (OSAO)

2020

Business Administration (OAMK)

2018-2019

SKILLS

- Unreal Engine
- Javascript, Typescript
- Python
- React, Next.js
- ThreeJS
- Blender

LANGUAGES

- Finnish
- English

PROFILE

Proven and hard-working problem solver with a 4 years of experience. My passion is combining my knowledge from various fields of technology including Software Engineering, 3D modeling, Game Development, Robotics, and WebGL to come up with efficient and bulletproof solutions to your problems at hand.

Worked with widely recognized clients including Nike, Fazer & Cartier

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sprint Al

9/2024 - Present

XR Developer

 Building an revolutionary XR professional athlete training and coaching platform leveraging AI

ZOAN

8/2023 - 8/2024

Software Engineer / XR Developer

- Full Stack web development (React, Typescript, Next.js, AWS)
- Unreal Engine Development (Immersive gaming- and virtual experiences)
- 3D Web development using ThreeJS
- Pixel Streaming

Probot Oy

4/2021 - 8/2023

Software Engineer

- Full Stack web development (React, Typescript, Next.js, AWS)
- Building remote controlled robotic systems using XR
- Building real-time and RESTful APIs for robotic systems and Unreal Engine

REFERENCES

Juri Saltbacka

ZOAN / Technical Director

Phone: +358406101558

Email: juri.saltbacka@gmail.com

Virpi Vaittinen

ZOAN / Producer

Phone: +358407367384

Email: vaittinen.virpi@gmail.com